<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Focus+</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>
    <string name="action_finish">Finish</string>
    <string name="action_delete">删除</string>
    <string name="history">History</string>


    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password (optional)</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>
    <string name="description_placeholder">This is a wonderful essay prompt.  It\'s a throwback to years past, before the advent of social media, 140 characters, and texting.  Think about it - if you were introduce yourself to your roommate for the first time in a good ol\' USPS-mailed letter, how would you approach the note?         Rattling off your accomplishments might come across as self-centered, but you\'d still most likely look for ways to display your personality and interests, while simultaneously finding out a bit more about your roomie\'s life.</string>
    <string name="action_finish_plan_card">标记为已完成</string>

    <string name="history_delete_alertdialog_title">项目删除</string>
    <string name="history_delete_alertdialog_content">你想要删除这个项目吗？（项目删除之后无法还原）</string>

    <string name="about_overall">  This time management app: Focus, is a personal app project made by Jeffrey Tan.
        \n\n Right now this very first version has integrated the basic functionality of projects management, time tracking and stats.
        \n\n However, the functionality is not complete and some bug still remains due to the lack of labor.
        \n\n If you have good advice for the app, feel free to contact me with the Feedback function. I am happy to hear your precious advice. Please look forward to the second version. :)</string>
    <string name="whats_next">The next version will focus on Time tracking and Stats.Possible functions include:\n\n
    1. Advance stats features that can provide more specific stats for each project\n
    2. More advanced Todo system that can plan your everyday\'s task.\n
    3. Integration of Pomodoro Technique to improve efficiency\n
    4. Better motivation module that may integrate different techniques to motivate you.\n\n
        Enjoy and look forward to the next version! :)
    </string>
</resources>
